<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Gary Cheung Portfolio</title>
    <link>http://ceegary.com/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Gary Cheung Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 15:30:19 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://ceegary.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Straitcast</title>
      <link>http://ceegary.com/projects/straitcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 15:30:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceegary.com/projects/straitcast/</guid>
      <description>About the project Straitcast is a web based podcast player that aims to provide a convenient, no-frills user interface for searching and finding single podcast episodes. It is powered by React in the frontend, served by a Node.js server and deployed on a heroku dyno. Firebase is used as a caching layer.
Tech Stack  Frontend  React Redux  Backend  Node.js (Express)  Database  Firebase</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Herd Immunity</title>
      <link>http://ceegary.com/projects/herd_immunity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:04:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceegary.com/projects/herd_immunity/</guid>
      <description>About the project I developed this explorable explanation project over the course of a month for my data visualization class. It provides an high level explaination of the how to measure the population requirements for group (herd) immunity from infectious dieases. Users are about to observe the spread of an disease in an interactive visualization where they can customize the strength the of a disease and the vaccine against it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EMX Systems</title>
      <link>http://ceegary.com/projects/emx_systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 22:16:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceegary.com/projects/emx_systems/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview  Summary This project was completed on behalf of our client, EMX Systems, a healthcare startup developing a medical record exchange system that aggregates patient records from separate electronic medical record(EMR) systems to provide doctors with faster and more complete information about their patients. I worked as a UX researcher and designer on a team of five to assess the needs of medical professionals and design the frontend interface using our research findings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MoMA and Art Movements</title>
      <link>http://ceegary.com/projects/moma_art/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 22:16:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceegary.com/projects/moma_art/</guid>
      <description> About the project Our team of four worked with a dataset containing the nearly complete record of the Museum of Modern Art&amp;rsquo;s collection of works to visualize geographic changes in how the collection grew during each major modern art movement. We used Python with the pandas library to clean the dataset and D3.js to implement map and bar chart visualizations.
 impressionism &amp;amp; post impression movements geographic and work classification breakdown    Baubaus movement geographic and work classification breakdown   Project Links View Live Site   Source Code   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U-M Auxiliary Marketing Work</title>
      <link>http://ceegary.com/projects/aux_marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 15:30:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceegary.com/projects/aux_marketing/</guid>
      <description> Overview As a web developer on the University of Michigan&amp;rsquo;s auxiliary marketing team, I was responsible for maintaining several student life and university services used by the university&amp;rsquo;s students, staff, and visitors.

Conference and Events  Catering  Recsports  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MCommunity</title>
      <link>http://ceegary.com/projects/mcommunity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:24:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceegary.com/projects/mcommunity/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview  Who is the client? MCommunity is an online people directory built by the IT Services department within the University of Michigan. The directory has two main uses – for members of university of look up contact information about other people affiliated with the University, and building “groups” for official and student organizations which be used as an alternative to listservs for mass emailing.
Research Objectives The team working the MCommunity platform has began work on a new beta platform and has asked our team to conduct user experience research to determine the inclusion of new features and improvements on existing features.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>