<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gary Cheung UX Portfolio</title>
    <link>http://ceegary.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Gary Cheung UX Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 17:07:22 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://ceegary.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>EMX Systems</title>
      <link>http://ceegary.com/project/emx-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 17:07:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceegary.com/project/emx-systems/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview Summary EMX Systems is a healthcare technology company based in Michigan developing a health information exchange platform to improve medical record exchange between healthcare providers who use different electronic medical records (EMR) systems. The most popular EMR solutions, which store electronic patient records, cannot communicate to access each others records. Our client is developing software that supplements a provider’s existing EMR to make record exchange possible. Their platform includes an intranet web application, EMX Portal, for providers to securely access patient records from any other provider regardless of the originating EMR.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moment</title>
      <link>http://ceegary.com/project/moment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 17:08:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceegary.com/project/moment/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview Summary Moment is a UX research &amp;amp; design project that explores the use of personal informatics for data collection and analysis. For this project, our team of four designers chose a topic that was personal to all of us &amp;ndash; academic stress. Special focus was placed on developing an accurate data collection strategy which would promote behavioral change.
We designed an wearable &amp;amp; companion mobile app that measueres the strength of various stress coping mechanisms in order to provide in-the-moment feedback on the user’s fluctuating stress levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Driven Detroit</title>
      <link>http://ceegary.com/project/data-driven-detroit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 17:09:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceegary.com/project/data-driven-detroit/</guid>
      <description>Overview The Client Data Driven Detroit(D3) is a civic tech startup located in downtown Detroit that aims to support the revitalization of Detroit by providing data-driven evidence to the city’s government and local non-profit organizations. D3 tasked our group with the challenge of improving their organization’s interval data management processes so that they can complete projects in a more timely and efficient manner.
The Problem D3’s current methods for handling data internally do not scale with the increasing demand for their services and it is slowing down their current projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MCommunity</title>
      <link>http://ceegary.com/project/mcommunity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 17:35:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceegary.com/project/mcommunity/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview Summary MCommunity is a identity management platform and people directory for the University of Michigan developed by the university’s IT services(ITS) department. The platform is being rebuilt from the ground up to be better compatible with modern browsers and to improve the user experience of the platform. During the January of 2017, ITS tasked our group of five user researchers with completing an in-depth evaluation of the beta platform and advising them on the usability of their beta platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Explorable Explanations</title>
      <link>http://ceegary.com/project/data-visualizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 17:37:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceegary.com/project/data-visualizations/</guid>
      <description>Herd Immunity Visualization Summary I developed this explorable explanation project over the course of a month for my data visualization class. It provides an high level explaination of how to measure the population requirements for group (herd) immunity from infectious diseases. Users are about to observe the spread of an disease in an interactive visualization where they can customize the strength the of a disease and the vaccine against it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphic Design Collection</title>
      <link>http://ceegary.com/project/gd-collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 01:09:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ceegary.com/project/gd-collection/</guid>
      <description>Building Girls Protective Assets Layout design and typesetting for a 56-page book on designing girls&amp;rsquo; education programs in developing countries. Project was done as part of my role as a graphic designer for Population Council.
Deadly Weather Visualization Mockup of a data visualization on deadly weather for Arkadium&amp;rsquo;s Inhabit. Completed as part of my internship with Arkadium.
Ending Eclampsia Bookmarks Promotional bookmarks for created for Population Council&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Ending Eclampsia&amp;rdquo; campaign.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>